We all know children love to play with toys.
我们都知道孩子们喜欢玩玩具。
But as they approach adulthood, they stop being playful and concentrate on grown-up things – or so we believe.
但随着他们长大，他们就不再玩耍，专注于成年人的事情——至少我们是这样认为的。
However, in recent times at least, adults are revisiting their childhood and buying toys for themselves – and they've been given the nickname 'kidults'.
然而，至少近年来，成年人正在重温童年，为自己购买玩具——他们被赋予了一个绰号"童心未泯的成年人"。
There are many reasons for the rise of the kidult, but it's certainly big business.
"童心未泯的成年人"现象兴起的原因有很多，但这无疑是大生意。
In the USA for example, the Toy Association says that over half of adults bought toys and games for themselves last year.
例如，在美国，玩具协会表示，去年超过一半的成年人给自己买了玩具和游戏。
Nostalgia is part of the reason: people want to relive their childhood and now have the disposable income to do so.
怀旧是一部分原因：人们想重温童年，现在有了可支配收入来实现这一点。
Puzzles and board games are traditional toys that can be enjoyed at any age.
拼图和棋盘游戏是任何年龄段都可以享受的传统玩具。
But there's more to being a big kid than just taking a trip down memory lane.
但做个"大孩子"不仅仅是一次回忆过去之旅。
People have more time to let their hair down and play.
人们有更多时间放松和玩耍。
Hobbies such as modelling and construction with plastic bricks can help people develop skills into adulthood.
诸如用塑料积木建模和建造之类的爱好可以帮助人们在成年后发展技能。
And they allow people to switch off and relax.
它们还能让人们暂时放下烦恼，放松身心。
In fact, Frederique Tutt, global industry analyst at NPD, told the BBC: "I'd say much of this is providing an escape from the stresses and strains of modern-day living, fulfilling our need to find downtime."
事实上，NPD的全球行业分析师弗雷德里克·图特告诉BBC："我想说，这样做很多时候可以逃避现代生活的压力和紧张，满足我们暂时逃离的需求。"
Some people are even finding comfort and camaraderie by playing with others.
有些人甚至通过与他人一起玩耍找到了慰藉和友情。
Although competing with others through video gaming might be nothing new, others are coming together to build train sets or sophisticated models.
虽然通过电子游戏与他人竞争可能并不新鲜，但其他人则聚在一起建造火车模型或复杂的模型。
In Brighton in the UK, for example, Brighton Bricks is a club where adult fans of the toy Lego meet up every month to talk, play and swap collections.
例如，在英国布莱顿，有一个名为"布莱顿积木"的俱乐部，乐高玩具的成年粉丝们每月聚会一次，聊天、玩耍和交换收藏品。
But those who think playing with toys is childish and immature should take note of the research by René Proyer, professor of psychology at Martin Luther University Halle-Wittenberg in Germany.
但那些认为玩玩具是幼稚和不成熟的人，应该留意德国哈勒-维滕贝格马丁·路德大学心理学教授勒内·普罗耶的研究。
It suggests that adults who demonstrate more playful personality traits are more motivated, creative and spontaneous.
研究表明，展现出更多玩乐人格特质的成年人更有内驱力、更有创造力、也更自发自觉。
So, it seems life shouldn't be all work and no play, and maybe we should take play more seriously!
所以，生活似乎不应该只工作不玩耍，也许我们应该更认真地对待玩耍！